Hello, my name is Hana Kojima of Amefras. I am Hana Kojima from Ameflas.
And is it this way? Or is it that way? Or is it HARIMU? Is it HARIMU? I'm HARIMU?
Thank you very much.
Speaking of the two of us,
I think we are the members of Miyujichi's first union, aren't we?
That's right.
And we have been together for a long time.
Since the time of DVD rear.
About 10 years.
But, we have been together since we joined Harimaga Namie,
July 18 is the second anniversary.
Two years have passed.
Already two years?
That's quite a while.
That's really fast.
Didn't it feel like that?
I still feel like a new member.
Maybe I don't feel like a new member anymore.
No more?
Maybe not anymore.
You don't want me to feel like a young member?
They are already here. I'm sitting here.
Still fresh, like a new member.
We're not new members.
Really?Really?
When did you stop feeling fresh?
About five years ago.
Why is that?
Second anniversary.
I see. Namie's 3rd anniversary already.
Last time.
Because we changed it.
That's right.
Oh no.
But I think..,
I think that the members of Namiie used to get along well with each other,
But since Haniman joined the group, we've become more united,
I'm glad to see the unity or the good friendship.
I'm grateful for that.
Yay!
Isn't it great to have someone like Haniman in the group?
Haniman.
Is it? Is it great?
It's a great presence. You know what I mean.
It's not that great.
You know what I mean. I do.
I don't know. I don't know.
You don't know. You know you have a strong presence.
You think you have a big voice.I think they have a big voice.
But really, the Namie Women's Pressure Union,
But really, the Mimie Women's Pressure Union has two of the loudest voices in STAPLA, don't you think?
That's right. Yuzu and Yuzu and Niiman.
Yuzu and Niiman.
Yuzu and Niiman are there.
They are loud.
Even Yuzu was noisy enough,
But now that Haniman has come in, it's getting louder.
It's a lot louder.
But you know what? On the bus ride home from Namie, only Yuzu and Hana were awake.
Yuzu and Hana were the only ones awake.
Everyone else would fall asleep.
Atorupan would stay up with us.
He was so kind.
I know you would like to see them.
He keeps us company.
After Haniman came, Yuzu and Hana were very happy.
Bus fun.
The bus ride home is fun.
They get so excited, don't they?
I wonder what they are talking about.
I don't remember, but it's fun.
I don't know what they're talking about.
It's fun, isn't it?It's kind of fun, isn't it?
Good.
Because Haniman came in,
It's so much more noisy and fun now that Haniman is here.
Really? I'm glad.
I was so nervous at first.
You were first introduced at Bay Hall, right?
Were you really nervous?
Of course you were.
New members feel like they are joining the existing members.
It's not like it's the first time to meet someone.
That's why expectations go up.
When it comes to new members, I wonder who will be there.
I wondered who would be there.
You are the same as usual, Shunsui.
I can certainly understand that feeling.
That's why I was so nervous,
That's the nervousness.
We met on the same day, right?
That's what Namie said.
So I don't know how to get into it.
I had been watching live performances on YouTube,
But you don't know the backstage or rehearsal atmosphere.
I wonder what it's like.
I thought, "Arline is in the rehearsal room, right?He said, "Aaryn is at the rehearsal.
That's how it started.
So I was pretty nervous.
Even at that time, we weren't used to having Aaryn at rehearsals,
I still can't get used to it.
I still can't get used to it, but I'm getting used to it.
He talks to me a lot these days,
After all, we went to Disney!
I went to Disney! Yay!
No, I'm really happy!
I'm so happy!
I've never been able to go to Disney with Arline in my life.
No, no, no, no, no.
No way.
No way, but you know what?
We promised to go to the next Seek.
Then we'll go to Universe, and after that we'll go overseas.
Like, let's go to Disneyland overseas.
Yes!
You'll never go there, will you?
We might go.
Everyone has a passport.
I can go.
But it was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.It was fun.
We all had a great time at Disney.
What? Have you ever been to the Onlys like that?
No, no, no.
No, not like that.
It was my first time too.
There were at most five of us.
That's right.
Fun.
That was fun.
It was fun, and you were in charge.
Like, "Hana-chan, I'll go here next.
That's right. I like Disney.
Everything was like a timetable.
I didn't think about the timetable.
Are you serious?
But I don't know,
Let's go here next.
Oh, you're hungry?
All of them.
Like, "Oh, let's have dinner together.
I thought, "Wow, that's great.
I wanted to have a good time.
I thought he was reliable.
But Harima's voice was so loud.No - but Harima's voice was so loud.
Even at Disney?
Of course,
When you're riding on attractions, you know?
I would say, "Crikey!
And there were attractions that you had to ride in a line
And there was this attraction that you could ride in a single line,
There was an attraction where you could ride in a line, and all 8 of us rode it together.
We all rode in a row, and I could hear the cries of excitement,
I thought, "I've jumped into the Moskie world.
I thought for sure it was going to be Harima-chan,
I thought that she was very close to me,
I wondered if she was next to me.
I wondered if she was there,
I was at the very end of the line,
I was at the end of the line, and I said, "Wait a minute.
I was at the very end.
What's wrong with the end?
I was at the end of the street, and it was so noisy,
I felt bad for Aaryn.
Yeah, that's why I said, "Poor Aaryn, her ears are so loud.
Poor Aaryn. I really feel sorry for her.
But I'm leaving.
I was going to.
It's not right.It's funny.
When the video is like falling in a really scary place,
I can understand if it's a cry.
I can understand if you cackle just before you fall.
What are you scared of? It's like, "What are you scared of?
You know how you almost collide with it once?
There's also "caw.
Like, "You're just trying to say 'caw'.
No, no, no.
When you're having fun, you're going to cackle, right?
Well, yeah.
But you were noisy too, Hagoromo.
I have a tendency to be loud.
You were really loud during Splash.
Splash is because, you know.
Because, listen to me.
During the splash, Hagoromo was suddenly at the very back.
Four rows.
Four rows from the front, I was in the third row and Hagoromo was in the fourth row,
Suddenly, she started to shout.
You were shouting, weren't you?
I started to make my voice.
She started to do voice training.
It was really noisy.
They suddenly did something weird.Suddenly they do weird things.
Splash was the loudest.
Splash was so much fun.
Yuzu sang next to me,
Yuzu sang next to me and opened an opera by himself.
They were harmonizing with Splash's music.
We were harmonizing with the music of Splash.
Splash twice.
It was a lot of fun.
We did a lot of Nami, Jojo, and Tsugumi,
We just entered our third year.
I am looking forward to the future.
I look forward to working with you.
We will be together forever. Your idol life.
That's right.
Let's do our best.
Now, in this nighttime idol dialogue series,
I've prepared some questions that I'd like to ask each other,
I've prepared some questions that I'd like to ask each other.
I'll go first.
I'll ask Harima a question.
What is it?
Is it actually a character?
In fact.
I guess we have an image of her,We have an image of him,
Harima-san is actually very smart, isn't he?
He is a bit calculating.
You are a little bit smart, aren't you?
I've been with you for a long time.
You are serious. I have the image of a very serious person.
I have an image of a hard-working, hard-trying person.
I wonder how he really is.
Is he a character?
Is he a character or not?
If you ask me if I'm a house or not, I'm not a character.
It's more like this,
But if you dig deeper..,
I'm exaggerating a bit.
But I did think that I've always had this kind of personality,
I wondered if I was always this noisy at home.
Maybe I'm like this at home, too.
It's fun. And then...
It's fun.
But it's true that I feel like I'm alone.
Of course.
You're smart, Mr. Sugaya,
I don't know. I don't know that much about him.
I just have this image of you.
That's why I thought it was great.So I thought it was great.
Really?
I've been around since the days when people were talking about 100% foreheads like this.
But I want you to hear about the 100% forehead. That was a calculation, too.
Oh, really?
When I was in 3B Junior, I introduced myself,
I knew you didn't have bangs.
You didn't have bangs, and you usually had your hair parted in a fashionable way, like a parting of the hair into 7 thirds,
But she was wearing her hair in twin-tails with a center parting and no bangs.
Normally, I would have thought that there must have been a prettier hairstyle,
I could have made it look more cute, but I didn't. I had to make it tactile. I could have curled it or something,
Pikahn! Pekahn! Hee! I was like, "Oh, my God!
And once I asked a member, "Why do you keep doing your hair like that?
What? Who are you?
I was asked once. On the train on the way home.
He asked me in a serious tone,
I thought I had to answer him properly,
I came out and said that I had been wearing my hair that way because I thought it would stand out more,
I did exaggerate some things, but not everything,
But not all of it.
I was talking about how my personality is the same as before,
So you were exaggerating a bit with the 100% forehead.
I'm glad to know. I'm glad to know.
It's been bothering me for a long time.
It was bothering me.I was wondering.
Then I have a question for Hana-chan,
Hana-chan, you used to be like a cute little boku-chan,
But suddenly you became a handsome guy.
I have the image of the handsome Hana-chan that you have become so well established,
Is it something that comes naturally to you?
I think it's hard to answer whether it's something that comes naturally to Hana-chan, or whether it's something that she's studied.
Hana-chan is the type of person who doesn't show that she is making an effort.
So I thought I shouldn't ask too much,
It's not often that I get an opportunity like this,
I'm really interested in how you do your research.
But I'm curious to know how you are doing your research,
I started to lose my bangs when the staff asked me to do without them,
But after I started getting comments that I was good looking,
I studied so that I could be really good looking.
I like to be cute,
I really want to dance pretty and look pretty,
I really want to dance cute and look cute, but I also think that looking good suits me better and makes me unique.
So, I looked at good-looking dancers so that I could be good-looking,
I also tried my best to be popular in terms of appearance.
I think it's amazing. I think it's great.
Thank you very much.
I'm too good-looking for social networking and TikTok.
I really think so,
There are boyish girls who are like that to begin with,There are boyish girls who are like that to begin with,
What? I thought, "What?
I mean, I have always had that vibe, but..,
But when I revisited my memories, I thought, "No, that's not right.
I didn't used to be like that.
That's right. I like the cute look.
Like Boku-chan.
I do a lot of cute birthday parties,
I thought you must like cute things.
I knew it. That's right.
But I'm glad. You said I was cool.
Really? He's cool and funny.
Like your mimicry.
It's funny to see your mimicry on Twitter,
It makes me want to send him a lip or something.
I even want to send him a flirtatious kiss.
Sometimes, I get a lot of complaints.
That's right.
The other day, we were lip-syncing each other.
They were talking on Twitter the whole time.
I told them that they should definitely do it on LINE.
Because I know that Hana-chan is the one who will go along with that kind of thing,
I can do something.
Really, but we've been talking about Harimata too.
What's with this talk? I don't like it.What's this story? I don't like it.
I don't like it.
I don't want to hear it.
That's what I wanted to hear.
We've been together for a long time, haven't we?
There's no one else I'm this close with, so let's stay together from now on.
Let's be good friends.
Let's be good friends. That's how we ended up having this conversation today,
It was fun.
It was fun. We don't often have a chance to talk together, do we?
We don't talk unless we have an opportunity to do so.
We don't talk about serious things, basically.
I can't bring it up, and I've forgotten how to talk about serious things.
We've never had a serious talk.
We only talk about joking around.
That's why I'm glad. I'm glad you gave me this opportunity.
I hope you will continue to support Harima and Hana Kojima.
Thank you very much.
So, in our meeting so far,
Kojima and Hana Kojima of Amefurashi,
I hope you will continue to support us.
Bye bye!